Finding Aid for Sam Sturgis Photograph collection
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Ann Arbor
  - AA 501 - AA 550
    - J. R. Hayden. Exterior of a barbershop whose awning reads "the ideal" and a photographic supply store with "Kodaks" in the window. 1912, AA 517 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Mrs. JR Hayden. Photographer: Lyndon.)
    - Israel Hall residence at 1129 Washtenaw Ave. on 15 March 1912. 1912, AA 518 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Fred Wagner and Bros. Blacksmith., AA 519.1 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Ann Arbor High School Football in 1908. 1908, AA 519.2 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Hertler Bros. Labor Day Parade., AA 519.3 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Bartenders and brewery workers in 1918. 1918, AA 520 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Mary Hunt.)
    - Feiner Glass, First National Bank and Philip Bach Store on Main St., AA 521 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Harrar Building on Liberty St. in 1952. 1952, AA 522 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Eck Stanger.)
    - Packard and Huron Sts. Line streetcar., AA 523 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.1 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.2 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.3 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.4 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.5 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.6 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.7 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.8 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.9 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.10 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.11 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.12 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.13 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.14 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.15 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Railroad wreck at Michigan Central Railroad Depot on 16 September 1940. 1940, AA 524.16 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Otto's Band., AA 525.1 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Otto's Band., AA 525.2 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Otto's Band., AA 525.3 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Germania Hall Group., AA 526 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - North side Liberty St. between Main and Ashley Sts., AA 527 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Burton Tower Bells., AA 528.1 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Burton Tower Bells., AA 528.2 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Burton Tower Bells., AA 528.3 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Weinman and Hoelzle. Also site of Fischer's Hardware during early 1980s. 1912, AA 529 --; copy neg.
    - Torch Papers., AA 530 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Michigan Historical collections. Wheeler House on Huron St.)
    - Torch Papers., AA 531 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Michigan Historical Collections. Chase Building and later Kyer-Whitker Wholesale Grocers in 1930s at Main and Miller Sts.)
    - Torch Papers., AA 532 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Michigan Historical Collections. Wheeler House on W. Huron St.)
    - Torch Papers., AA 533 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Michigan Historical Collections. Huron Block opposite Exchange Block and Ingalls St.)
    - Torch Papers., AA 534 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: (Michigan Historical Collections. Norman Covert House, built 1845 on Dexter Road at Huron-Jackson Rd.)
    - Torch Papers., AA 535 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: .Michigan Historical Collections. Campbell House on Packard Road.)
    - Torch Papers., AA 536 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Michigan Historical Collections. Broadway and Pontiac Trail.)
    - Torch Papers., AA 537 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Michigan Historical Collections. Gas station at Main and Packard Sts.)
    - Torch Papers., AA 538 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Michigan Historical Collections. Building southside Broadway and Wall St.)
    - Torch Papers., AA 539 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Michigan Historical Collections. George Corsehie residence at 317E. Ann St.)
    - Torch Papers., AA 540 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Michigan Historical Collections. Building on SE corner Catherine and Detroit Sts.)
    - Splitt Family porch on Pauline Blvd with Ernie, Ed and Karl Splitt, Karl Mahlke and John Behnke., AA 541 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source and photographer: Wystan Stevens and Ernie Splitt.)
    - Ernie Splitt in front of Schutzend Bund Park on Pauline Blvd, now Fritz Park., AA 542 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source and photographer: Stevens and Splitt.)
    - Otto's Band during Spring 1914 from photo on North University Ave. 1914, AA 543 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Scenic view of Ann Arbor., AA 544 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Ann Arbor Fluff Rug Company and Neon Signs., AA 545 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - River St. looking north c. 1908 in Milan, MI. 1908, AA 546 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Hotel Simpson c. 1909 in Milan, MI. 1909, AA 547 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - St. Paul's Evangelist Church c. 1912 in Saline, MI. 1912, AA 548 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Whitmore Lake, Michigan., AA 549 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - View of Willis, Michigan looking east., AA 550 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
  - AA 551 - AA 600
    - Clifton House at Whitmore Lake, MI. 1911, AA 551 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Wahr residence at 324 S. Ashley St. on 2 May 1900 with Fred B. Wahr, Chas. W. Wahr and Agnes M. Wahr. 1900, AA 552 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Razing of UM's Old Clocktower., AA 551 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Razing of UM's Old Clocktower., AA 552 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Fred B. Wahr and Miller Footwear., AA 553A --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Razing of UM's Old Clocktower., AA 553B --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Campbell family group portrait., AA 554 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Street scene., AA 555 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - All-male group portrait., AA 556 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Site of Jolly Bar in 1970s. Former site of Atlantic and Pacific Company (A&P) store., AA 557 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Mitchell's Barber Shop at 117 W. Washington St., AA 558 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - 115-117 West Washington St., AA 559 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Unloading circus train on Depot St. in 1913. 1913, AA 560 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Circus train near Depot St. in 1913. 1913, AA 561 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Circus parade on 300 block South Main St. in 1913. 1913, AA 562 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Circus parade on 300 block South Main St. in 1913. 1913, AA 563 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Circus parade on 300 block South Main St. in 1913. Present site of Kline's Department Store. 1913, AA 565 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Circus parade on 300 block South Main St. in 1913. 1913, AA 564 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - South Main St. at Liberty St., AA 566 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Mack's Garage in former German Church at northeast corner West Washington and First Sts., AA 567 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Ann Arbor Newsboys in 1892,including African-American children. 1892, AA 568 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Northwest corner Main and Huron Sts. c. 1927. 1927, AA 569 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: UM Alumnus.)
    - Portrait of Christian Eberbach, pharmacist who died 1901. Lived at 1115 Woodlawn Drive., AA 570 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Interior of 1129 Washtenaw Ave, site of Ruthven Museum. Home of Israel and Olivia Hall., AA 571 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Residence at 1530 Hill St., AA 572 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Residence at 1530 Hill St., AA 574 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Israel and Olivia Hall in their home at 1129 Washtenaw Ave. site of Ruthven Museum., AA 573 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Israel and Olivia Hall in their home at 1129 Washtenaw Ave., site of Ruthven Museum. Interior., AA 575 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Interior of Israel and Olivia Hall residence at 1129 Washtenaw Ave., site of Ruthven Museum., AA 576 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Interior of Israel and Olivia Hall residence at 1129 Washtenaw Ave., site of Ruthven Museum., AA 577 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Interior of Israel and Olivia Hall residence at 1129 Washtenaw Ave., site of Ruthven Museum., AA 578 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Abandoned building., AA 579 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
      (Source and/or photographer: Stimson?)
    - Photo of a woman., AA 580 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
    - Washtenaw Hotel. Glass neg., AA 581 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
      (Photographer and Source: Stimson.)
      [See also AA221.34]
    - Island Park Bridge and water scene., AA 582 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
      (Source and/or photographer: Stimson.)
    - Civil War Memorial in cemetery., AA 583 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
    - Winter scene including decaying building from Argo Mill fire., AA 584 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Stimson.)
    - String orchestra., AA 585 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Ed H. Pierce., AA 586 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - View of Main St. looking south in 1910. 1910, AA 587 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
    - View of Broadway from river c. 1922. 1922, AA 588 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
    - Winter train accident, Ann Arbor Railroad., AA 589 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
    - winter train accident, Ann Arbor Railroad., AA 590 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
    - Winter train accident, Ann Arbor Railroad., AA 591 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
    - Winter train accident, Ann Arbor Railroad., AA 592 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
    - Panoramic view of Ann Arbor from Sunset Blvd., AA 593 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
    - Automobile., AA 594 --; Glass neg. (Box 4)
    - Ann Arbor Hardware Store., AA 595 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Ann Arbor Hardware Store., AA 596 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Wedding photos c. 1902. 1902, AA 597 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Corner of Catherine and Detroit Sts. during winter., AA 598 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: City of Ann Arbor.)
    - Corner of North University Ave. and State St. in March 1951. 1951, AA 599 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
  - AA 600 - AA 650
    - Train wreck., AA 600 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: city of Ann Arbor.)
    - Train wreck., AA 601 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Train wreck., AA 602 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Train wreck., AA 604 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Train wreck., AA 605 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Three men in street scene. From left to right: William Koppler, M. Howard, F. Baker. 1948, AA 606 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Northern approach of Old Broadway Bridge., AA 608 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Snow removal car at Maynard and William Sts. 1941, AA 609 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - North University Ave., AA 610 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Main at William Sts., AA 611 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Northern approach of Old Broadway Bridge., AA 612 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Northern approach of Old Broadway Bridge in August 1948. 1948, AA 613 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Northern approach of Old Broadway Bridge., AA 614 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - City Unity House in 1934. 1934, AA 615 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - [Undated], AA 616 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 4)
    - 1937, AA 617 --; copy neg. Future grocery store front at 702 Dewey St. on 2 Dec. 1937. (Box 4)
    - 1937, AA 618 --; copy neg. Future grocery store front at 702 Dewey St. on 2 Dec. 1937. (Box 4)
    - Corner of Main and Packard - Motor Service Garage., AA 618a -- (Box 4)
    - 1941, AA 619 --; copy neg. Farmers Market construction c. 1941. (Box 4)
    - 1941, AA 620 --; copy neg Farmer's Market construction c. 1941. (Box 4)
    - [Undated], AA 621 --; copy neg. Construction FM radio tower on East Huron Street. (Box 4)
    - 1938, AA 622 --; copy neg. Bandshell construction begun in West Park on 24 March 1938. (Box 4)
    - 1938, AA 623 --; copy neg. Construction begun in West Park for bandshell on 24 March 1938. (Box 4)
    - 1943, AA 624 --; copy neg. Flood at Island Park c. 1943. (Box 4)
    - 1943, AA 625 --; copy neg. Flood at Island Park c. 1943. (Box 4)
    - Flood at Island Park., AA 625a -- (Box 4)
    - 1943, AA 626 --; copy neg. Winter scene on Longshore Drive, Jan. 20, 1943. (Box 4)
    - 1943, AA 627 --; copy neg. Winter scene on South State St. near Hill St. on 19 Jan. 1943. (Box 4)
    - 1943, AA 628 --; copy neg. Jan. 20 1943, winter scene on Longshore Drive. (Box 4)
    - 1943, AA 629 --; copy neg. Winter scene on Longshore Drive on 20 Jan. 1943. (Box 4)
    - 1943, AA 630 --; copy neg. Winter scene at State St. south of Packard St. on 19 Jan. 1943. (Box 4)
    - 1943, AA 631 --; copy neg Brooklyn St. near Packard St. in 1943. (Box 4)
    - 1943, AA 632 --; copy neg. Photo AA-632 is Packard St. west of Brooklyn St. Photo AA-632A is Beakes and Division Sts. Both winter scenes on 19 Jan. 1943. (Box 4)
    - 1943, AA 633 --; copy neg. Riverside Park winter scene on 19 Jan. 1943. (Box 4)
    - 1942, AA 634 --; copy neg. RML Removal Project on Catherine St. in 1942. (Box 4)
    - 1942, AA 635 --; copy neg. RML Removal Project on Catherine St. in 1942. (Box 4)
    - [Undescribed], AA 636 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 4)
    - [Undescribed], AA 637 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 4)
    - First Tailor Shop at 108 E. Washington St. in 1888. 1888, AA 638 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
      (Source: Allmendinger Family Album.)
    - Northwest corner First and Washington Sts. c. 1900, Ann Arbor Organ Works, Allmendinger family business. circa 1900, AA 639 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Scenic view of AA facing northeast. circa 1900, AA 640 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Scenic view of AA facing north. circa 1900, AA 641 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Scenic view of AA facing south. circa 1900, AA 642 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St. near State St. Il Genevievell during March 1954. 1954, AA 643 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Main control panel at Michigan Theater on Liberty St. in 1928. 1928, AA 644 --; copy neg. Photographer: George F. Korvin. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St., pit orchestra in 1928. 1928, AA 645 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St., WBBY display c. 1929-1930, during "Joy Month." 1929, AA 646 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St., WBBY display c. 1929-1930 during "Joy Month." 1929, AA 647 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Interior Michigan Theater on Liberty St. with Mr. & Mrs. Gerald Hoag and Van or Ian Johnson., AA 648 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St., interior and ticket seller., AA 649 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - UM Glee Club outside Michigan Theater on Liberty St. before 1956. circa 1955, AA 650 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
  - AA 651 - AA M7
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St. circa 1930. circa 1930, AA 651 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St. with Henry Aldridge, intermission organist., AA 652 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St. circa 1945. circa 1945, AA 653 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St. circa 1947-1949. circa 1947-1949, AA 654 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St., AA 655 --; copy neg. No print. Interior exhibit. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St., AA 656 --; copy neg. No print. Interior exhibit of refrigerators. (Box 4)
    - Michigan Theater on Liberty St, interior exhibit., AA 657 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Winter view of Ann Arbor with "cat hole" in center and Observatory in left distance., AA 658 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - First National Bank, exterior., AA 659 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Ann Arbor business district including John E. Hunt, C.H. Millen and Company and Philip Bach and Company., AA 660 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Business district including exterior of Eberbach Hardware Company., AA 661 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Main St. looking north in the 1920s(?). circa 1920, AA 662 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - State St. looking north in the 1920s (?). circa 1920, AA 663 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - B. St. James Dry Goods and Carpets on main St., AA 664 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Exterior of Hale and Smith Bank., AA 665 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Public gathering in courthouse square during 1860s. People are listening to speech about firing on Fort Sumter (1861)? circa 1865, AA 666 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Old University Hall with excavation, possibly for Angell Hall in the 1920s. circa 1920, AA 667 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Residences and livery stable (?)., AA 668 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Methodist Church., AA 669 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 4)
    - UM students on central campus near cannon and flagpole c. 1915 circa 1915, AA 670 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Polhemus Hack, Omnibus and Transfer Office on Main St., AA 671 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - UM musical Club leaving for western trip in 1913. 1913, AA 672 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 4)
    - R and B Clothing., AA 673 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 4)
    - Exterior of Seegar Meat Market., AA 674 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 4)
    - UM professors' house on North University Ave. (the northwest residences?), AA 675 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Old Methodist Church on State St. with Ann Arbor High School on right., AA 676 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Group portrait in front of professor's house and UM buildings., AA 677 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - UM's West Physics Building., AA 678 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - UM's Harris Hall at corner of Huron and State Sts., AA 679 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Psi Upsilon Fraternity House at State St. and South University Ave., AA 680 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Huron River above Foster's Station, Barton Hills in background., AA 681 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Post Office at corner Main and Ann Sts., AA 682 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Staebler and Sons, used automobiles in 1918. 1918, AA 683 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company (A&P) and Mitchell's Barber Shop., AA 684 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Mitchell's Barber Shop., AA 685 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Exterior of Detroit Edison building at southeast corner Main and William Sts. in 1923. 1923, AA 686 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Exterior of Detroit Edison building at southeast corner Main and William Sts. 1923, AA 687 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Men's Shop in Nickels Arcade (?) Van Boven?., AA 688 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Staebler's Garage (?), AA 689 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Entrance of First National Bank c. 1929. Photographer Randall from Armstrong Studio. 1929, AA 690 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Interior of First National Bank c. 1929 with floral arrangements. Photographer Randall from Armstrong Studio. 1929, AA 691 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Interior of First National Bank c. 1929. Photographer Randall from Armstrong Studio. 1929, AA 692 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Interior of First National Bank c. 1929 including safety deposit vault. Photographer Randall from Armstrong Studio. 1929, AA 693 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Construction of building., AA 694 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Brick building., AA 695 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Washtenaw Hotel on Broadway. Wood building., AA 696 --; copy neg. 9A 6rOJW Al (Box 4)
    - Elisha Jones School on North Division St., AA 697 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - W.S. Perry School on Packard and Madison Sts. built 1903., AA 698 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - View of State St. at North University Ave. from campus c. 1890 (?). circa 1890, AA 699 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Football game, UM v. University of Pennsylvania at first football stadium, Ferry Field in 1914. 1914, AA 700 --; copy neg. Photographer: Randall. (Box 4)
    - UM Golf Club c. 1910 (?). circa 1910, AA 701 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Lits Smoker at the Michigan Union on 3 December between 1915 and 1920. (1918 date listed in info.), AA 702 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Winners of Freshman-Sophomore Contest in 1918. Photographer: Lyndon. 1918, AA 703 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - "The Fight," greased pole fight at Ferry Field c. 1910. circa 1910, AA 704 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - UM's McMillen Hall., AA 705 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Tappan School on East University Ave., built 1893., AA 706 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - German Methodist Church, built 1896 at northeast corner Fourth Ave. and Jefferson St. Used since 1950 by Reorganized Church of Latter Day Saints., AA 707 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Old Presbyterian Church at southwest corner Huron and Division Sts. First occupied in 1862, photo taken c. 1910, razed in 1935. circa 1910, AA 708 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - English Lutheran Church/Trinity Lutheran Church at Fifth Ave. and William St., built 1895., AA 709 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Bethlehem German Church on Fourth Ave., built 1895., AA 710 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - St. Thomas Catholic Church, built 1897-99 and designed by Frederick Spier, on North State St. c. 1903. 1903, AA 711 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Church of Christ c. 1920. Church was dismantled and rebuilt in reverse at corner Tappan and Hill Sts. as Memorial Christian Church. circa 1920, AA 712 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Detroit Edison's Barton Power Plant., AA 713 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Detroit Edison Steam Generating Plant along Michigan Central Railroad tracks., AA 714 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - The former Vivienne Farms on Old Huron River Drive near Dixboro, site of Detroit Edison Conference Center., AA 715 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Old YMCA building on Fourth Ave., AA 716 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Corner of Main and Washington Sts., looking northeast c. 1910. circa 1910, AA 717 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Fischell and Finnell Cigar Store at corner Packard and State Sts. c. 1910. circa 1910, AA 718 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - Whitney Theater at southwest corner Main and Ann Sts. c. 1910. circa 1910, AA 719 --; copy neg. (Box 4)
    - View of Farmer's Market on east lawn of Old Courthouse and YMCA on Fourth Ave., AA 720 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 4)
    - Stephen Barker portrait. Son of UM prof. Ernst Barker. Residence interior at 18 Ridgeway., AA 721.1 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Paul Barker portrait. Son of UM prof. Ernst Barker. Residence interior at 18 Ridgeway., AA 721.2 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Stephen and Paul Barker, sons of UM prof. Ernst Barker. Residence interior at 18 Ridgeway., AA 721.3 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Stephen and Paul Barker, sons of UM prof. Ernst Barker inside residence at 18 Ridgeway., AA 721.4 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - The Ernst Barker family, UM professor, inside residence at 18 Ridgeway., AA 721.5 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Stephen and Ernst Barker, sons of UM prof. Ernst Barker at 18 Ridgeway., AA 721.6 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Paul Barker, son of UM prof. Ernst Barker, inside residence at 18 Ridgeway., AA 721.7 --; No neg. (Box 4)
    - Men in laboratory in 1916. 1916, AA 730 --; No print. (Box 4)
    - Horse-drawn parade float. Independence Day?, AA 731 --; No print. (Box 4)
    - Women at drinking fountain., AA 732 --; No print. (Box 4)
    - Men loading horse and cart., AA 733 --; No print. (Box 4)
    - Gathering in Courthouse Square., AA 734 --; No print. (Box 4)
    - Portrait of gentleman c. 1922? 1922, AA 735 --; No print. (Box 4)
    - Crowd gathered at race track., AA 736 --; No print. (Box 4)